{
    "id": "0cd375f5c6d144e1b40e11e2c91c330d",
    "title": "Agreements And Disagreements",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "‘You don’t like him.’ ‘Yes, I ………………’",
            "description": "Disagreements with negative statements are made with yes+ pronoun + auxiliary verb",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "don't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "322ed1f37c974c9d85a109349f6ac65e"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘She doesn’t have a job.’ ‘……………………, she doesn’t.’",
            "description": "Agreements with negative statements are made with ‘No + pronoun + auxiliary + n’t / not’.",
            "answers": [
                "Yes",
                "No"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "caa76f119b4a4bf5b10d7a87bfd9586d"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘It is a great film.’ ‘No, it …………………..’",
            "description": "Disagreements with affirmative statements are made with ‘No + pronoun + auxiliary + n’t/not’.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "isn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "573d8765c36c40f898babc9e49c76ce4"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rocky cannot swim. ……………………… can I.",
            "description": "Negative additions to negative statements are made with nor / neither + auxiliary + subject.",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "940a81378a224c378b64eb59b79c0c0e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She wasn’t late but you ……………………..",
            "description": "Affirmative additions to negative remarks are made with but + subject + auxiliary.",
            "answers": [
                "were",
                "weren't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3036d439c88541a0b72c683225e4577a"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘He is drunk.’ ‘No, he ……………………..’",
            "description": "Disagreements with affirmative statements are made with ‘no + pronoun + auxiliary + n’t/not’.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "isn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b1fd0d50cbb8444f96e476edb5e24e41"
        },
        {
            "question": "He can speak German very well. ……………………….. can I.",
            "description": "Affirmative additions to affirmative remarks are made with so + auxiliary + pronoun.",
            "answers": [
                "So",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "14eee8bef6f3497e9f4c1fccb70591c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘He won’t come again.’ ‘Yes, he ………………………’",
            "description": "Disagreements with negative statements are made with yes+ pronoun + auxiliary verb.",
            "answers": [
                "will",
                "won't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b6a5a06d7d2646e9a13c116842b1e32c"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I didn’t break it.’ ‘Yes, you ……………………..’",
            "description": "Disagreements with negative statements are made with yes+ pronoun + auxiliary verb",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "didn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "926a368431f3429eb3f03b16861df97a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Tom wasn’t there. ………………………… was his brother.",
            "description": "Negative additions to negative remarks are made with ‘nor / neither + auxiliary + subject’.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "So",
                "Either"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "83bc76a4bae842d7997175de9654a09b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I loved the movie but my brother ………………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did",
                "didn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2c0c96ee64244777825382116d5ea148"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘You don’t know him.’ ‘Yes, I …………………………..’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "didn't"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "229051bbe4a9493fb7d929bac2270661"
        }
    ]
}